how'd you come up with all this stuff I
look up and it's right there I thought
you were gonna get makeup that's too
late now
all right you know that I have I have
done this show so many times I think
I've done it three more times than you
have you do very well on it I do well
I'm surprised you're still here because
I thought I would be replacing you by
now there was the rumor all right we've
got to get to Ben Affleck I was making
fun of him earlier but Ben Affleck's
nice guy he had a good time at a
Halloween party over the weekend let's
take a look at a clip from TMZ that
noise after it makes you feel guilty
that was actually happen that noise Oh
in this clip hit the car it has an alarm
it sounds like yeah it's like a
law-and-order sting for real-life people
but I feel like TMZ is exploiting
celebrities lately it's not my
imagination I just like that people like
Hollywood changes you and he's like no
I'm from Boston drinks that's right he
also has a phoenix tattoo so it's like
he's not reached rock bottom yet you
know yeah I like the old days when the
paparazzi was like if they had Sinatra
to permeate like hey Frank oh my god
that's not your wife oh I'm so sorry
rip out film burn and they were holding
the flash with one hand I just thought
he looked at was super happy yeah
finally yeah yeah I know when he's sober
he's just angry now he looks like having
a good time
he's like finally drunk and single I do
like that there's a new thing go someone
out of him because he's on riah oh yeah
you know the dating app it's a celebrity
dating app Ania announced he joining cuz
after someone said he did we leave this
guy alone for two seconds let him go on
a date I mean good guy but the thing
about going on Araya for him is why does
he need Riya I mean I mean he's Ben
Affleck I think he just likes to reject
no no no if he was on rye that's gonna
be like the hunger games for girls with
8,000 followers and there's no chance
for me now oh you're on Ryan nine
dollars last night he made Batman yeah
that's true
he's doing but I'm actually on riot ooh
but I go into the name Ben Affleck I
loud a screenshot on Raya oh no one
knows that you boned marshmallow the DJ
anyway let me just ask you one question
about writing in all seriousness with
Raya do you need like a computer or
device together
[Laughter]
[Music]